<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LLM Pathology Knowledge graph</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- {{if .Params.image_url}} --&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;image-container&#34; style=&#34;display: block;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/Dataset_files/Pathology_Knowledge_Graph.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- {{end}} --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- 首字母大写 --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;intro-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    his project has constructed a pathology knowledge graph covering 20 common diseases, with data sourced from the relevant clinical guidelines published by the National Health Commission of China. By utilizing graphRAG and large language models, we have structured the diagnostic processes, symptom presentations, examination methods, treatment plans, and more for these diseases. We performed entity recognition and relationship extraction on the textual data, automatically constructing nodes and edges within the knowledge graph. The result is a knowledge graph designed for use in medical research, clinical decision support, and disease management systems, helping researchers explore potential disease correlations and develop innovative treatment methods. By integrating large language models, this system also provides doctors with diagnostic insights, treatment suggestions, and personalized medical plans, improving both diagnostic efficiency and accuracy.&#xA;      &lt;!-- &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;      t present, a part of the publicly available pathological image pairs data sets such as Quilt are obtained from crawlers on social networks. However, there are some problems in Quilt dataset, such as non-pathological images mixed in pictures, non-pathological descriptions in text, and incorrect correspondence between pictures and text. These data have adverse effects on the training of multimodal models, which makes the performance of the models on downstream tasks worse. Data filtering can filter out data at a high noise level, and models trained on clean subsets will get better performance on downstream tasks. --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;img class=&#34;col-img&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/collaborate/liver_cancer.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;The collaboration project between Wuhan Tongji Hospital and our laboratory began in July 2023. The collaboration focuses on exploring the recurrence patterns of liver cancer based on liver WSI slices. We utilized AI annotation tools to efficiently complete the identification and segmentation tasks of over 800 H&amp;amp;E and IHC slices, segmenting the most relevant liver cancer tumor regions on the WSI. Compared to traditional manual annotation methods, this approach saved 86% of the time.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;The segmented image data, used as a key data item in downstream recurrence pattern classification tasks, improved the AUC from 0.72 to 0.79.&lt;/div&gt; --&gt; &#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/product_files/Non-pathological_Image_Filtering.png&#34; alt=&#34;Project 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-pathological Image Filtering</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- &lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/product_files/Non-pathological_Image_Filtering.png&#34; alt=&#34;Project 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/lbp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/lbp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;With the development of AI technology, especially in the medical field, machine learning and deep learning technologies have provided new possibilities for pathology diagnosis and research. The collaboration between the laboratory and Guangzhou Anbiping Medical Technology Co., Ltd. (referred to as &amp;ldquo;Anbiping&amp;rdquo;) aims to integrate the strengths of both parties, focusing on the intelligent development of pathology diagnosis. This includes the integration and enhancement of multimodal medical data, medical image data annotation and processing based on crowdsourcing and knowledge graphs, as well as data-centric explainable medical artificial intelligence and other related cutting-edge topics. The goal is to enhance pathology diagnosis services and the value of medical data, promoting high-quality development in the pathology industry.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;This collaborative project officially launched in May 2023. The research projects conducted by the laboratory include crowdsourcing annotation of medical data, weakly supervised learning for medical AI tasks, and research on the explainability of medical AI tasks.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;col-img&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/collaborate/LBP_MDI_establish.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;Currently, we have built an automatic annotation platform that can accurately label pathology images such as immunohistochemistry and immunofluorescence. Pathologists using this platform have provided feedback indicating a 50% reduction in annotation time. We have also developed a large language model with pathology knowledge, which demonstrates good diagnostic abilities for given pathology images. We will continue to optimize existing data models, aiming to reach the level of junior pathology doctors in image interpretation and diagnosis. Additionally, we are conducting data mining on stored pathology images and unstructured pathology data such as text descriptions, providing a solid data foundation for pathology research.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;col-img&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/collaborate/LBP_data_mining.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;Pathology is the &amp;ldquo;gold standard&amp;rdquo; for tumor diagnosis, and cancer prevention and control rely heavily on pathology diagnosis. As pathology diagnosis transitions towards digitization and intelligence, the standardization and efficient annotation of pathology data have become critical challenges in the transformation process. Anbiping is the first listed company in the domestic pathology diagnosis field, specializing in the research and development of pathology diagnosis-related technical products. Their cervical liquid-based cytology image-assisted diagnosis software (LBP-PIAS) has achieved technological breakthroughs in medical image analysis and clinical diagnostic assistance. In this context, Professor Chen Lei, the head of the laboratory, pointed out that in the current field of machine learning, models and hardware resources are relatively abundant, while high-quality data resources are extremely scarce. He hopes that through collaboration with Anbiping, the shift from a &amp;ldquo;model-centric&amp;rdquo; approach to a &amp;ldquo;data-centric&amp;rdquo; approach can be achieved. By breaking down complex medical tasks into simpler tasks that junior medical workers can handle, the cost of data acquisition can be reduced. Utilizing a large amount of automatically annotated simple task data to improve AI diagnostic accuracy, fully tapping into the potential value of pathology data. By quantifying medical indicators, extracting diagnostic rules, providing data-based explainability, addressing the pain points in the intelligent pathology diagnosis process, and contributing to the intelligent pathology diagnosis in China and even worldwide, benefiting society through precise medical diagnosis.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaned Pathology Image-Caption Dataset (public)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- &lt;div class=&#34;image-container&#34; style=&#34;display: block;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/Dataset_files/Pathology_Knowledge_Graph.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- {{end}} --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- 首字母大写 --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;intro-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    he pathological image and text dataset collected and organized from public mainly consists of pathological images and their corresponding textual annotations obtained from open sources such as social media platforms, forums, medical papers, pathology tutorial videos, and textbooks. These image-text pairs have been applied with basic cleaning and curation, with descriptions outside the domain of pathology and low-readability textual annotations being removed. The dataset contains valuable multimodal knowledge and their corresponding relationships defined in the area of pathology.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLLM Evaluation in Breast Cancer</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/project/project2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/xh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/xh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;In collaboration with Peking Union Medical College and Shenzhen Maternal and Child Health Care Hospital, we integrate histopathological H&amp;amp;E stained slides and p16 stained images to develop a deep learning algorithm for binary classification (LSIL- and HSIL+) of cervical tissue pathology samples. This initiative aims to create an efficient, accurate, and reliable artificial intelligence diagnostic system for cervical cancer genomics pathology images. The goal is to enhance the accuracy of early cervical cancer diagnosis, shorten the time and process of pathological diagnosis, reduce the costs associated with patient treatment and diagnosis, and improve the level of public health and medical services.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;col-img&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/collaborate/xh_1.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;col-img&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/collaborate/xh_2.png&#34;&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/xh_col/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/xh_col/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;col-img&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/collaborate/xh_col.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;Colposcopy is a technique used to screen and diagnose abnormalities in the cervix, vagina, and other areas in women. The interpretation of colposcopy reports often includes specialized terminology and complex medical data, which can be difficult for the average patient to understand. Additionally, doctors face the challenge of improving diagnostic and communication efficiency. Our collaboration with Peking Union Medical College and Shenzhen Maternity &amp;amp; Child Healthcare Hospital aims to address this issue by developing an intelligent interpretation system. This system will enable patients to easily understand their reports and gain a deeper understanding of their health status. At the same time, it will provide doctors with technical support and personalized diagnostic recommendations based on the reports, enhancing diagnostic accuracy and service quality, and improving communication efficiency between doctors and patients.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaned Pathology Image-Caption Dataset (all)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;intro-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    he pathological image and text dataset collected and organized from both public and non-public primarily includes pathological images and their corresponding textual annotations obtained from open sources such as social media platforms, forums, medical papers, pathology tutorial videos, and textbooks, as well as pathological reports and teaching notes from more specialized cooperative institutions and hospitals that are not publicly accessible. These image-text pairs have been applied with basic cleaning and curation, with descriptions outside the domain of pathology and low-readability textual annotations being removed. The dataset contains more precise multimodal knowledge and corresponding relationships defined in the area of pathology.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling law for pathology</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/project/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/project/project3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breast Cancer LLM Evaluation Benchmark</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;intro-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    e have developed a breast cancer benchmark to evaluate the performance of artificial intelligence models in pathological image analysis. We obtained 10 whole-slide images (WSIs) from collaborating hospitals, which were annotated by professional pathologists for six key breast cancer features: necrosis, perineural invasion, calcification, lymphovascular invasion, ductal carcinoma in situ (DCIS), and invasive ductal carcinoma (IDC). This resulted in approximately 1,000 high-quality images. Using these data, we evaluated multimodal large language models (MLLMs) and CLIP-like models on the six breast cancer diagnostic tasks. For CLIP models, we used predefined templates and synonym lists, assessing performance based on similarity scores between input images and preset text descriptions. For MLLM models, we combined templates and prompts to guide the models to respond with \&#34;yes\&#34; or \&#34;no\&#34; when answering pathology-related questions. Through this breast cancer benchmark, we aim to assess the performance of artificial intelligence models in pathological image analysis, provide a unified platform for researchers, and promote the advancement of artificial intelligence in the field of breast cancer diagnosis.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAM-based Image-Caption Generation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/project/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/project/project4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/tj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/tj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;col-img&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/collaborate/liver_cancer.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;The collaboration project between Wuhan Tongji Hospital and our laboratory began in July 2023. The collaboration focuses on exploring the recurrence patterns of liver cancer based on liver WSI slices. We utilized AI annotation tools to efficiently complete the identification and segmentation tasks of over 800 H&amp;amp;E and IHC slices, segmenting the most relevant liver cancer tumor regions on the WSI. Compared to traditional manual annotation methods, this approach saved 86% of the time.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;The segmented image data, used as a key data item in downstream recurrence pattern classification tasks, improved the AUC from 0.72 to 0.79.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/product_files/Non-pathological_Image_Filtering.png&#34; alt=&#34;Project 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KB-enhanced Pathology CLIP (public datasets)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/project/project5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/project/project5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/ger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/ger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;This project aims to develop and validate a multimodal AI model for predicting the efficacy of various drug therapies in treating Gastroesophageal Reflux (GER) symptoms. GER symptoms arise from the abnormal reflux of stomach and duodenal contents into the esophagus, causing esophageal and extra-esophageal symptoms or complications. Based on the Rome IV criteria, GER symptom patients are categorized into GERD (including erosive esophagitis and non-erosive reflux disease, NERD) and functional esophageal disorders (such as reflux hypersensitivity, RH, and functional heartburn, FH). Given the distinct pathophysiological mechanisms among these subtypes, current treatments like proton pump inhibitors (PPIs) are often suboptimal, with up to 50% of patients showing partial or no response. This project integrates multidimensional data including patient clinical information, endoscopic images, high-resolution esophageal manometry, and dynamic pH-impedance monitoring to build an AI model that accurately predicts the efficacy of various treatment regimens for GER symptoms, providing personalized medication guidance for clinicians.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/product_files/Non-pathological_Image_Filtering.png&#34; alt=&#34;Project 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathology Image-Caption Evaluation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/project/project6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/project/project6/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/hb4_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/hb4_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;Hebei Medical University Fourth Hospital and the Joint Intelligent Medical Data Experiment Center of the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (Guangzhou) officially launched a joint research project in September 2024, focusing on predicting the mutation status of the PIK3CA gene based on HE slices and the efficacy of neoadjuvant therapy. The project aims to address common challenges in the field of precision medicine, particularly in the treatment of breast cancer patients, by improving the efficacy of neoadjuvant therapy through efficient and accurate gene mutation prediction.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;In this project, both parties collaborate using cutting-edge artificial intelligence and deep learning algorithms, combined with large-scale pathological HE slice data, to develop an intelligent model for accurate prediction of PIK3CA mutation status. By integrating pathological images with genetic mutation analysis, we aim to achieve efficient and non-invasive mutation status prediction, providing more personalized and optimized treatment options for breast cancer patients.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;Significant progress has been made in the collaboration, with initial achievements including the establishment of a high-quality pathological image database and early validation of algorithm models. In the future, both parties will further optimize the model, advance its clinical application, and expect technology to demonstrate great potential in predicting the efficacy of neoadjuvant therapy for breast cancer.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;This collaboration brings significant benefits to both parties: Hebei Medical University Fourth Hospital further strengthens its research capabilities in medical data analysis and precision medicine through this project, promoting innovation within the institution; while the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (Guangzhou) applies the latest intelligent algorithm technologies directly to clinical practice through deep cooperation with medical institutions, further advancing the application of medical intelligence. Through this collaboration, both parties not only strengthen the bridge between academia and clinical practice but also provide broad possibilities for innovation in the field of precision medicine in the future.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/product_files/Non-pathological_Image_Filtering.png&#34; alt=&#34;Project 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-Caption Data Market Demo</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/project/project7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/project/project7/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/hb4_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/hb4_2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;Hebei Medical University Fourth Hospital and the Joint Intelligent Medical Data Experiment Center of the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (Guangzhou) officially launched a joint research project in September 2024 to establish a multi-modal deep learning model based on HE images and HER2 immunohistochemistry images for predicting the prognosis of metastatic breast cancer. This project integrates multi-modal data and applies deep learning technology to provide a more accurate and efficient method for breast cancer prognosis prediction, demonstrating significant clinical value and advancing the integration of artificial intelligence with medicine.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;Breast cancer is one of the most common malignant tumors in women globally, and HER2 is an important prognostic and predictive indicator for primary and metastatic breast cancer. Recently, novel antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs) have shown significant therapeutic effects in patients with late-stage HER2-low breast cancer, expanding treatment options beyond HER2-positive patients. However, HER2 expression in breast cancer exhibits spatial and temporal heterogeneity, and the discordance in HER2 expression between primary and metastatic lesions affects the efficacy and prognosis of patients receiving novel ADCs treatment. Accurate prognosis prediction for these patients is crucial for individualized treatment. Traditional prognosis prediction relies on clinical and pathological features, but these methods have limitations in accuracy and flexibility. The collaborative laboratory adopts a multi-modal deep learning approach, combining information from HE images and HER2 immunohistochemistry images to enhance the accuracy of predicting the prognosis of metastatic breast cancer. The core advantage of multi-modal deep learning models lies in their ability to integrate different types of data, automatically learn and extract key features from each modality, thus generating predictions with greater clinical relevance.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/hb4_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/collaboration/hb4_3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;We have established a deep collaborative relationship with the Fourth Hospital of Hebei Medical University, jointly dedicated to researching the application of artificial intelligence in the field of breast cancer. Our cooperation encompasses several key areas, including breast cancer whole-slide image (WSI) annotation, the construction of a breast cancer benchmark, and the development of a breast cancer multimodal large model. During our collaboration, both teams have engaged in close communication and cooperation, particularly on the breast cancer benchmark project. We have conducted in-depth discussions on the research directions of breast cancer, held detailed deliberations on data annotation methods, and thoroughly evaluated assessment methodologies.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;These efforts have ensured the accuracy and reliability of the benchmark. Through our close partnership with the Fourth Hospital of Hebei Medical University, we have leveraged our respective strengths, accelerating the progress of breast cancer research. &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;We believe that this collaboration will significantly contribute to the early diagnosis and treatment of breast cancer, making an important impact on the advancement of the medical field.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/product_files/Non-pathological_Image_Filtering.png&#34; alt=&#34;Project 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphRAG Based Pathology LLM</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/project/project8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/project/project8/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
