<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LLM Pathology Knowledge graph</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- {{if .Params.image_url}} --&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;image-container&#34; style=&#34;display: block;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/Dataset_files/Pathology_Knowledge_Graph.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- {{end}} --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- 首字母大写 --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;intro-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    his project has constructed a pathology knowledge graph covering 20 common diseases, with data sourced from the relevant clinical guidelines published by the National Health Commission of China. By utilizing graphRAG and large language models, we have structured the diagnostic processes, symptom presentations, examination methods, treatment plans, and more for these diseases. We performed entity recognition and relationship extraction on the textual data, automatically constructing nodes and edges within the knowledge graph. The result is a knowledge graph designed for use in medical research, clinical decision support, and disease management systems, helping researchers explore potential disease correlations and develop innovative treatment methods. By integrating large language models, this system also provides doctors with diagnostic insights, treatment suggestions, and personalized medical plans, improving both diagnostic efficiency and accuracy.&#xA;      &lt;!-- &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;      t present, a part of the publicly available pathological image pairs data sets such as Quilt are obtained from crawlers on social networks. However, there are some problems in Quilt dataset, such as non-pathological images mixed in pictures, non-pathological descriptions in text, and incorrect correspondence between pictures and text. These data have adverse effects on the training of multimodal models, which makes the performance of the models on downstream tasks worse. Data filtering can filter out data at a high noise level, and models trained on clean subsets will get better performance on downstream tasks. --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;img class=&#34;col-img&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/collaborate/liver_cancer.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;The collaboration project between Wuhan Tongji Hospital and our laboratory began in July 2023. The collaboration focuses on exploring the recurrence patterns of liver cancer based on liver WSI slices. We utilized AI annotation tools to efficiently complete the identification and segmentation tasks of over 800 H&amp;amp;E and IHC slices, segmenting the most relevant liver cancer tumor regions on the WSI. Compared to traditional manual annotation methods, this approach saved 86% of the time.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;col-text&#34;&gt;The segmented image data, used as a key data item in downstream recurrence pattern classification tasks, improved the AUC from 0.72 to 0.79.&lt;/div&gt; --&gt; &#xA;&lt;!-- &lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/product_files/Non-pathological_Image_Filtering.png&#34; alt=&#34;Project 1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaned Pathology Image-Caption Dataset (public)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- &lt;div class=&#34;image-container&#34; style=&#34;display: block;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/Dataset_files/Pathology_Knowledge_Graph.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- {{end}} --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- 首字母大写 --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;intro-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    he pathological image and text dataset collected and organized from public mainly consists of pathological images and their corresponding textual annotations obtained from open sources such as social media platforms, forums, medical papers, pathology tutorial videos, and textbooks. These image-text pairs have been applied with basic cleaning and curation, with descriptions outside the domain of pathology and low-readability textual annotations being removed. The dataset contains valuable multimodal knowledge and their corresponding relationships defined in the area of pathology.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaned Pathology Image-Caption Dataset (all)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;intro-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    he pathological image and text dataset collected and organized from both public and non-public primarily includes pathological images and their corresponding textual annotations obtained from open sources such as social media platforms, forums, medical papers, pathology tutorial videos, and textbooks, as well as pathological reports and teaching notes from more specialized cooperative institutions and hospitals that are not publicly accessible. These image-text pairs have been applied with basic cleaning and curation, with descriptions outside the domain of pathology and low-readability textual annotations being removed. The dataset contains more precise multimodal knowledge and corresponding relationships defined in the area of pathology.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breast Cancer LLM Evaluation Benchmark</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/dataset/dataset4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;intro-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;dropcap&#34;&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;    e have developed a breast cancer benchmark to evaluate the performance of artificial intelligence models in pathological image analysis. We obtained 10 whole-slide images (WSIs) from collaborating hospitals, which were annotated by professional pathologists for six key breast cancer features: necrosis, perineural invasion, calcification, lymphovascular invasion, ductal carcinoma in situ (DCIS), and invasive ductal carcinoma (IDC). This resulted in approximately 1,000 high-quality images. Using these data, we evaluated multimodal large language models (MLLMs) and CLIP-like models on the six breast cancer diagnostic tasks. For CLIP models, we used predefined templates and synonym lists, assessing performance based on similarity scores between input images and preset text descriptions. For MLLM models, we combined templates and prompts to guide the models to respond with \&#34;yes\&#34; or \&#34;no\&#34; when answering pathology-related questions. Through this breast cancer benchmark, we aim to assess the performance of artificial intelligence models in pathological image analysis, provide a unified platform for researchers, and promote the advancement of artificial intelligence in the field of breast cancer diagnosis.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
